# TAI MUJARIN

14333 Van Nuys Blvd #73 Arleta Ca, 91331 · (213) 448-7523 **Tai.mujarin@gmail.com** 

Highly experienced in customer relation and knowledgeable in hospitality field. Able to adapt to variety of assignments and adhered to Company policy and procedure. Open to building new skill set and challenges given. Obtain a highest degree of self-discipline and is motivated to take on new endeavor.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### 2008 - 2010

# **CHEF, WHOLEFOODS**

- Trained and certified with Wholefood's hot food service
- Culinary expertise in Japanese food preparation
- Experience in creating and preparing sushi on a daily rotation
- Able to create customize Sushi orders and develop new selection for management
- Successfully provide 5-star services for customers

#### 2010-2012

### **CARE GIVER, AGOURA HILLS SENIOR LIVING**

- Provide nurturing care and comfort to Seniors with daily living assistance
- Duties include bathing, toileting, dressing, grooming, feeding
- Assigned to Dementia Ward
- Assist LVN and RN with daily job functions and provide condition report to management
- Communicate and entertain Seniors with games, conversations, and other stimulating activities to help with Dementia
- Assist LVN and RN with intakes and reporting

#### 2010-2014

### MEDICAL TECHNICIAN, AGOURA HILLS SENIOR LIVING

- Promoted to Medical Technician within a year
- Able to administer daily medication to the Elderly and supervise intake of required medications
- Perform daily vital sign and continue to monitor and complete intake report for Patients
- Review and recommend reports to Nurses, Supervisors, and upper management on daily conditions of Elders
- Continue to perform the following: bathing, toileting, dressing, grooming, feeding
- Close interaction with Patients and provide unconditional respect and understanding for the Elders

#### 2014-2019

## MERCHANDISER, CORE-MARK

- Daily commute to multiple brick and mortar storefronts to oversee quality and quantity of products and QC pricing to meet Coremark standard
- Maintain highest level of customer service with Clients
- Responsible for stocking, pricing, rotation of products
- Due-diligent in reviewing expired items and interchanging items with credit to Clients to avoid health and hazard issues for Consumers.
- Manage ordering products and replenishing product and ensuring there is sufficient stock.
- Create and deliver invoices to Coremark without mishaps and errors
- Successful in providing solution and recommendation to upper management on workflow as a Merchandiser

# **EDUCATION**

JANUARY, 2011-2012

CASA LOMA NURSING COLLEGE, ASSOCIATE DEGREE

**AUGUST 12, 2010** 

ABRAHAM FRIEDMAN OCCUPATIONAL CTR, HIGH SCHOOL EQUIVALENCY CERTIFICATE

## **SKILLS**

- Excellent communication skills and self discipline
- Able to adapt to any environment

- Team leadership and provide peer support
- Certified Nurse Assistant
- Possess self-perseverance and flexible